<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Northwest C++ Users’ Group</title><link>http://nwcpp.org/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://nwcpp.org/feeds/rohit-patnaik.rss.xml" rel="self"></atom:link><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 00:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate><item><title>March 18th 2015: The Go Programming Language</title><link>http://nwcpp.org/march-2015.html</link><description>&lt;div class="section" id="time-and-location"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Time and&amp;nbsp;Location&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class="line-block"&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;March 18th, 2015 at 7:00 &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Steptoe Room, &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://nwcpp.org/steptoe-meeting-room.html"&gt;Cafeteria 40&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Microsoft Campus,&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;156th Ave &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NE&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Redmond, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WA&lt;/span&gt; 98052.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="abstract"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This talk will cover various aspects of the Go programming&amp;nbsp;language.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, you still have time to vote for the specific topic(s) you would like to have at: &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://campoy.cat/nwcpp"&gt;http://campoy.cat/nwcpp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="bio"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Bio&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Francesc Campoy Flores is a Developer Advocate for Go and the Cloud at Google. He joined the Go team in 2012 and since then he has written some considerable didactic resources and traveled the world attending conferences, organizing live courses, and meeting fellow gophers. He joined Google in 2011 as a backend software engineer working mostly in C++ and Python, but it was with Go that he rediscovered how fun programming can&amp;nbsp;be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find him on twitter as&amp;nbsp;&amp;#64;francesc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="a-word-from-our-sponsor"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;A Word From Our&amp;nbsp;Sponsor&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re thrilled to be a &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NWCPP&lt;/span&gt; sponsor! Xtreme Consulting is locally owned and headquartered in Kirkland, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;WA&lt;/span&gt;. We provide a wide-range of business and &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IT&lt;/span&gt; consulting solutions, managed services, and staff augmentation. We actively recruit for fun, smart, and career-driven &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IT&lt;/span&gt; professionals who bring an enthusiasm for personal growth and accelerating success for our clients. Xtreme’s consultants are provided the opportunity to work with and for some of the best technology companies in the industry. We work hard to create a passionate, supportive environment where employees can reach their career development goals, enjoy exceptional benefits, and have fun all at the same&amp;nbsp;time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xtreme focuses on solutions and services including analysis, design, architecture, development, testing, implementation, maintenance and support of a variety of software technologies with specific emphasis on portal development, technical content creation, virtual machine environments and client and server deployment. Visitxtremeconsulting.com for more information. You can view and apply to our open positions at &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.xtremeconsulting.com/careers"&gt;http://www.xtremeconsulting.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;.
Xtreme Contact: &lt;a class="reference external" href="mailto:info&amp;#64;xtremeconsulting.com"&gt;info&amp;#64;xtremeconsulting.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Rohit Patnaik</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>tag:nwcpp.org,2015-02-28:march-2015.html</guid></item></channel></rss>